欢迎来到波比[柬埔寨赌镇]
Welcome to Poipet.
你真漂亮
You are so beautiful.
走吧
Come on.
嘘
Sh.
住手 损坏的货可卖不了
Hey. You can't sell damaged merchandise.
装货上船
Put her in the shipment.
皮肉交易
新泽西州 纽瓦克市
泰国 曼谷
谢了
Thanks.
嗨 戴克斯
Hey, Dex.
把货带出来
Bring out the merchandise.
无意冒犯
Don't be offended.
不过对于核实客户的身份
We have a way of making sure our client are
我们有特殊的方法
who they said they are.
干她
Fuck her.
现在
Now.
在我们面前
And we watch.
还想谈判吗
You are negotiating huh?
现在
Now.
维克多・德拉戈维奇在泽西市
Victor Dragovic is in Jersey.
放屁 来做什么
Bullshit. Why?
不知道 我只知道这么多
I don't know, that's all that I know okay?
尼克 你根本不清楚你在对付谁
Look, Nick, you don't know who you're fucking with okay?
这些塞尔维亚人 可不像意大利人
These Serbs, they're not like the Italians.
该死的 甚至还不如俄罗斯人呢
Fuck, they're not even like the Russians, alright?
他们无法无天
They have no code.
不 等等 等等
No, no! Wait! Wait! Wait!
交货地点在哪
Where is the delivery?
拉我上去 我就说
Pull me up and I'll talk.
- 不要 - 在哪
- Ah! No! - Where?
等等
Wait.
新泽西码头
New Jersey docks.
货船是柬埔寨之星
The ship is called The Cambodian Star.
快把我拉上去
Now pull me up!
德拉戈维奇会去吗
Will Dragovic be there?
会 会 维克多・德拉戈维奇会去的
Yes, yes. Victor Dragovic will be there.
快把我拉上去
Now pull me up.
拉我上去
Pull me up.
求你 求你
Please. Please.
你可以带她走
You can have her.
免费 我保证
No charge, I promise.
她姐姐也送给你 行不
I'll throw her sister in too, okay? Huh?
求求你
Oh, please.
我把知道的都说了
I told you everything I know.
拜托 把我拉上去吧
Come on. Just pull me up.
谈判结束
Negotiation is over.
回到你父母身边去吧
别轻信陌生人
都说是基因让人类不朽
They say our genes are what make us immortal,
子孙继承我们的姓氏 传承
that our children will carry on our names, our legacy,
家族给予我们希望
that it is family that gives us hope.
我为你骄傲 安德鲁
I am proud of you Andre.
如为你兄弟们一般骄傲 伊万与戈兰
As I am of your brothers, Ivan and Goran.
[塞尔维亚-克罗地亚语]
Sretan rodendan, brat.
意思是生日快乐 弟弟
Means Happy Birthday kid brother.
我的四子詹科 无法列席
My fourth son Janko could not be here
但他送上了来自波比的诚挚祝福
but he sends best wishes from Poipet.
我的儿子 安德鲁
My son, Andre,
你我血脉相同
you and I have the same blood in our veins.
敬充满奇遇的未来
Here is to many good adventures.
愿我们千秋永存
May we all live long.
- 万岁 - 万岁
- Dug zivot. - Dug zivot.
卡西迪警探
Detective Cassidy.
我是特工里德 人口贩卖专案组
Special Agent Reed, Human Trafficking Task Force.
有什么我能为联邦调查局效劳的
What can I do for the FBI?
虽然我希望
Well, you know I'd hoped for
能多些跨机构合作
a little more inter-agency collaboration.
你们想独揽行动
You're trying to keep the operation contained.
- 防止... - 泄密 是的我明白
- Stop so... - Leaks. Yeah I understand.
听着 现在还不是太晚
Look, you know, it's not too late
把行动交给我们
to hand the op over to us, you know.
维克多・德拉戈维奇
Viktor Dragovic.
前塞尔维亚籍 现在在俄国活动
Ex-Serbian national, now working in Russia.
谢谢你迟到了
Thank you for coming in late.
德拉戈维奇靠酒店和赌博
Dragovic made a fortune in hotels and gambling
在东欧和亚洲发了财
in Eastern Europe and Asia.
但同时 他也深度参与人口贩卖
But he's also a major player in what I consider
在我眼里这是地球上最卑劣的恶行
the most despicable endeavor on Planet E, human trafficking.
德拉戈维奇在东南亚绑架年轻女孩
Dragovic kidnaps young girls in South East Asia,
把她们运至欧洲 再卖到世界各地
runs them through Europe then sells them all over the globe.
人皮交易价值数十亿美元
The skin trade's worth billions of dollars.
光去年 美国就有超过两千起案件
Last year alone this country saw over 2000 cases
我觉得每起案件都是场悲剧
and I consider every single one of those a goddamned tragedy.
这是德拉戈维奇的长子 戈兰
This is Dragovic's oldest son, Goran.
在英国读的书
Educated in England.
次子 伊万
Son number two, Ivan.
运作中东的活动
Runs the Middle East operation.
这是三子 安德鲁 可爱吧
This is son number three, Andre. Isn't he cute?
他是纽约大学的学生
He's a student at NYU.
最后是四子詹科
And there's a fourth son Janko
运作东南亚的贩卖活动
who runs the trafficking operations in South East Asia.
大家都认识尼克・卡西迪
Okay you all know Nick Cassidy.
他是这起特案的负责人
He's the case officer in this particular opus.
请继续 尼克
Take it away Nick.
今早 在哈德森河打捞出了
This morning we fished Dex Guroff,
线人戴克斯・古洛夫的尸体
an informant, out of the Hudson.
头部中了两枪
Two gunshot wounds to the head.
死前 戴克斯曾向我坦白
Before he was killed Dex confirmed to me
维克多・德拉戈维奇就在泽西市这里
that Viktor Dragovic is here in Jersey.
多谢来自泰国皇家警局的双边情报
Now thanks to shared bi-lateral intelligence
揭露了他来此的原因
by the Royal Thai Police, we know why.
更棒的是 还有地点
Better. We know where.
目标是一艘名为柬埔寨之星的船
Our target is the ship The Cambodian Star.
海岸警卫队证实 它在不到三小时前
The coast guard confirms it arrives at Pier 21
停泊在了泽西码头的二十一号位置
at the Jersey Docks in less than three hours.
女士们先生们 我们要确保
Ladies and gentlemen, we're going to make sure
来美国是维克多・德拉戈维奇此生
that coming to America was the worst decision
最糟糕的决定
Viktor Dragovic ever made.
安德鲁 放松
Andre, relax.
这是你的第一次行动 我会伴你左右
This time, your first time, I will be with you.
开门
Open door.
上 上
Go, go, go, go.
走
Move!
不是我的错
It's not my fault.
是詹科 你的儿子
Janko, your son.
那你呢
But you?
你才是船长
You are the boat skipper.
在我来的地方
Where I come from,
男人要为自己的行为负责
men are accountable for their actions.
今天 安德鲁 你要证明你是我的子嗣
Today, Andre, you will prove that you are your father's son.
我手上沾满鲜血 你也一样
The blood on my hands is the same as the blood on yours.
让我骄傲
Make me proud.
拜托
Please.
拜托 不 求你了
Please, no. Please!
我们是警察
This is the police.
立刻放下所有武器
If you have any weapons lie them down.
安德鲁
Andre!
左边包抄
Left side cover!
安德鲁
Andre!
守着他
Stay with him!
你必须走 安德鲁
You have to run, Andre.
他分不开身追我俩
He cannot chase us both.
- 我要同你作战 - 服从命令 安德鲁
- I want to fight with you. - Obey me Andre!
走
Run.
活下去
Survive.
我要向你证明... 我是你的子嗣
I'll prove to you... I am my father's son!
不
No!
这一刻 我等了一辈子了
I've waited my whole life for this moment.
我可不怕死
I am not afraid to die.
动手吧
Do it.
动手
Do it!
- 你还好吗 - 没事
- You okay? - Yeah.
天呐
Holy Christ.
德拉戈维奇先生对集装箱的情况并不知情
Mr. Dragovic was unaware of the contents of the container.
他坚称自己没有开火
He maintains he never fired a shot.
他和他的儿子安德鲁是你们
And that he and his son Andre were caught
在行动中误捕的
in your mishandled operation.
我的委托人是位有名望的商人
My client is a respected businessman
俄国和亚洲均是如此
in Russia and in Asia.
但在塞尔维亚可不是
But not in Serbia, though.
对吗 上校
Right, Colonel?
又回那里 你可真是冒险
Pretty dicey for you to go back there.
集装箱里的那些尸体
All those bodies in that container,
是否让你想起以前种族屠杀的日子
did they give you a little buzz on your old genocide days?
德拉戈维奇先生已被
Mr. Dragovic was exonerated
海牙国际法庭宣告无罪
by the International Crimes Tribunal in the Hague.
他现在是俄国公民
He is a Russian citizen now.
我们已经联系了俄国政府 而你...
The Russian government have been contacted and you...
- 打扰了 队长 - 什么事
- Excuse me, Captain. - Yeah?
马上回来
Be right back.
- 这是谁 里德 - 俄方律师
- Who's this, Reed? - Russian counsel.
罗曼诺夫先生 这是科斯特洛队长
Mr. Romanov, this is Captain Costello.
我与华盛顿的俄国大使馆沟通过了
I spoke to the Russian embassy in Washington.
我是来监察当事人人权的
I'm here to monitor my client's human rights.
真的吗 他的人权
Really? His human rights?
你在跟我开玩笑吗
Are you fucking kidding me?
我没把你眼球戳出来算你走运
You're lucky I don't poke your fucking eyes out.
他走了告诉我一声 里德
Let me know when he's gone, Reed.
我要用集装箱里的每一具尸体
I'm going to wrap every dead body
告你到生不如死
from that container around your neck.
三十宗谋杀
30 counts of murder.
你该在船坞杀了我的 探长
You should have killed me in that dockyard, Detective.
你晚上怎能入睡
How the hell can you sleep at night?
怎能下如此的手
How can you do this?
买卖人命
Buy and sell human lives.
问我的顾客去吧
Ask my customers.
几时他们不买了 我就不卖了
When they stop buying, I stop selling.
戈兰 伊万
Goran. Ivan.
你推荐的那个船长
The skipper you recommended?
他搞砸了
He fucked up.
警察知道了货的事情
The police know about the delivery.
詹科
Janko.
我们的小兄弟死了
Our baby brother is dead.
父亲进了监狱
Father in prison!
我们在美国政府的所有联络人
All our contacts in the government over there
必须马上过来
will have to come over soon.
俄国以后不会再管我们了
Russia won't take us anymore.
这次别他妈再搞砸了
And don't you fuck this one up.
- 我... - 你也是家人
- I... - You're family, okay?
是血亲
You're blood.
就算你是妓女生的
Even if it is diluted whore's blood.
是谁杀了安德鲁
And Andre's killer?
你别管这个
Don't you fucking worry about that.
血浓于水
进来
Come on in.
詹科 选了你
Janko here, he has picked you
给他拍部电影
to be in one of his movies.
说句"干我屁股"试试
Now can you say, 'fuck my ass'
用你可爱的口音
in that lovely accent of yours?
起来
Get up!
托尼 美国人抓了维克多
Tony, the Americans, they have Viktor.
我们知道
We know.
他的儿子们想把他弄出去
The sons, they try to get him out.
他们在政府有联系人
They have contact in government.
他们还想复仇
They want revenge, too,
干掉那个杀了小儿子安德鲁的警察
against the cop that killed the youngest, Andre.
敏
Min.
别再当线人了
You should stop this work.
太危险
It's dangerous.
我打电话给警察送信的时候
When I call the police and give information
他们说会保护我
they said they would protect me.
对 每次都会
We have. Every time.
只要你调查这案子 我就继续
So as long as you are on the case, I do what I do.
也许这样能阻止我的悲剧
Maybe it stop what happened to me
在其他女孩身上重演
happening to other girls.
看看你练得如何
Let's see what you got.
好的
Okay.
出自莎士比亚戏剧《暴风雨》
假如你曾用法术 亲爱的父亲
If by your art, my dearest father,
使狂暴的海水兴起这风浪 请让它们平息
you have put the wild waters in this roar, allay them.
天空似乎要泼下发臭的沥青
The sky, it seems, would pour down stinking pitch,
但海水将腾涌到天空之颊
But that the sea, mounting to th' welkin's cheek,
将火焰浇熄
dashes the fire out.
我看到世间的痛苦 我亦痛之切肤
Oh, I have suffered with those that I saw suffer.
周五就这样表演
You do exactly that on Friday.
你会去吗
You'll be there?
你的每个重要时刻我不是都在吗
Haven't I been there at all the important moments of your life?
没
No.
你没有
You haven't.
什么
What?
你俩合伙对付我是吧
Are you two ganging up on me?
好了 你睡吧
Alright, you get some sleep.
我还要去处理个 案子
I'm going to have to deal with this, this uh... this criminal.
怎么了
What's wrong?
集装箱里的姑娘们和苏菲亚同年纪
The girls in that crate were Sofia's age.
至少她还有你的保护
At least she has you looking out for her.
我今天盯着一个人的眼睛
Today I stared into a man's eyes
看不到任何情感
and knew nothing was looking back.
怎么会那样
How does that happen?
今天是什么日子
What date is it today?
糟糕 我忘了
Shit. I forgot.
十三年了
Thirteen years.
我会送你全纽约最美的玫瑰
Look I'll get you the most beautiful roses in New York
明天一早 我保证
tomorrow morning. I promise.
你可能忘了 但我没忘
You may forget, but I don't.
周年快乐
Happy anniversary.
又怎么了
What now?
这么早就工作 我都说了别接电话
Are you even gonna start? I said no phone calls.
是科斯特洛 必须得接
It's Costello. I gotta take it.
喂
Yeah?
尼克 我是科斯特洛
Hey Nick, it's Costello.
我刚跟曼谷的泰国警方通了电话
I just got off the phone with the Thai police in Bangkok.
听着 维克多・德拉戈维奇...
Listen, Viktor Dragovic is...
罗莎
Rosa!
尼克
Nick.
为我们兄弟报仇
This is for our brother.
不
No!
爸爸
Dad?
苏菲亚 回去
Sofia, get back.
爸爸
Dad!
别杀我
Please don't.
爸爸
Dad!
天呐 尼克
Jesus, Nick.
尼克 能听见吗
Nick, can you hear me?
是科斯特洛和里德
It's Costello and Reed.
我知道你很难受
I know this is hard
而且我们可能是现在世界上
and we're probably the last two guys in the world
你最不想理的两个人了
you want to talk to right now.
时间地点都不合适
It's the wrong time and place.
我们走吧
Let's get out of here.
尼克
Nick?
罗莎
Rosa.
苏菲亚
Sofia.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
尼克
Nick.
罗莎和苏菲亚都死了
Rosa and Sofia are dead.
她们的尸体已被大火吞噬
Their bodies were consumed by the blaze.
消防员在楼下找到你
The firefighters found you downstairs.
德拉戈维奇
Dragovic?
他不见了
He's gone.
因外交压力 法官允许他进行保释
Diplomatic pressure convinced the judge to grant him bail.
他一离开就逃走了
As soon as he was on the street he was in the air.
我们无能为力
There was nothing we could do.
俄罗斯人不会带他走的
Russians wouldn't take him.
我们猜他可能是在泰国或者柬埔寨
We think he's somewhere in Thailand, maybe Cambodia.
尼克 你现在不要想太多
Nick, you don't need to think about this right now, man.
伙计们送了你这张卡片
All the guys sent you this card
我就放在这里了
and I'm going to put it right here.
葬礼已经举办了
There was a funeral.
德拉戈维奇给了你多少钱做法律顾问
How much did Dragovic pay you counsel?
我是外交官 我有豁免权
I'm a diplomat. I have immunity!
我还有妻子 孩子
I have a wife! Children!
我以前也有
So did I.
维克多在哪里
Where's Viktor?
哪里
Where?!
波比 柬埔寨 洋娃娃迪厅
Poipet, Cambodia. Baby Doll.
柬埔寨
维克多
Viktor.
你必须得走了
You have to move on.
我只能保你到这里了
There's nothing more I can do.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
只能保我到这里
Nothing more you can do.
美国人很坚决 泰国人也是
The Americans are insisting, and the Thai too.
他们施加了巨大的政治压力
They are applying heavy political pressure.
我不能一直否认你躲在这里
I can't keep denying that you are here forever.
只能到这里了
There's only so much I can do
否则他们会有疑问的
without them asking questions.
甚至会有政治后果
There can be political consequences.
这照片里的女人 可不是你妻子
The woman in the photo, she is not your wife.
下张照片的女孩呢
And the girl in the next one?
大概和你女儿的年纪相仿
She is about the same age as your daughter.
好吧
Okay.
我试试再撑两周
I'll try for two more weeks.
但之后你必须要去老挝了
But then you must leave for Laos.
那就够了
That works.
嘿 嘿
Hey hey!
我说了不要乱跑
No running I said!
我要为你们的发展实施计划 儿子们
I want to put in place a plan for you, my sons.
让你们接手公司
To take over the companies.
戈兰 你负责所有在
You, Goran, will oversee all the operations
俄罗斯 乌克兰 白俄罗斯的运作
in Russia, Ukraine, Belarus.
伊万你负责罗马尼亚 保加利亚 匈牙利
Ivan, you will take over Romania, Bulgaria, Hungary,
还有捷克
Czech Republic.
你们两人同时负责在东南亚
Both of you will oversee expanding trafficking,
扩张贩卖交易
South East Asia.
詹科呢
Janko?
曼谷
噢 噢 噢
Oh, oh, oh!
不错吧 我在进步
Not bad huh? I'm getting good!
我喜欢会打架的女人
I like a girl who can fight.
二十一道刀伤 七个香烟烫痕
21 cuts, 7 cigarette burns.
他们把你从越南带去德国时 你多大
How old were you when they took you from Vietnam to Germany?
十二岁
Twelve.
知道吗 我记得我妈当时很不开心
You know, I remember my mother was really upset
因为她只拿到了七百美元 而不是一千
because she only got $700 and not $1000.
你在帮她吗
不管你的事
好妞儿都让你占了 都不分享
想想家里的好妞儿吧
带着孩子 围着灶台的那些
快点走吧 他们在楼下等着
里德特工来自联邦调查局 人口贩卖专案组
Agent Reed is from the FBI's Human Trafficking Task Force.
这位是特组队长托尼・维塔雅科
This is special branch major Tony Vitayakul,
还有他的搭档 农警长
his partner, Captain Nung.
这是一段目击者拍摄的手机视频
This is cell phone footage shot by a guest
事发地点在维克多・德拉戈维奇的律师开在纽约的餐馆
at a New York restaurant owned by Viktor Dragovic's attorney.
...柬埔寨 洋娃娃迪厅
...Cambodia, Baby Doll.
注意看背景
Watch the background.
他搭飞机到了达拉斯
He took a plane to Dallas.
在那里我们追踪到他去了墨西哥城
From there we tracked him to Mexico City
那里可以买到伪造美国护照
where he could buy a fake American passport
只要一千美元不到
for under $1000.
但他是从告密小贼手上买的
But he bought it from a snitch
所以警方知晓了他的行踪
and you know how these things pan out.
我们认为现在尼克的情绪
We think Nick is suffering from a severe
极其不稳定
psychological breakdown.
尼克的班机十八分钟前刚降落
Nick's plane landed exactly 18 minutes ago.
我侥幸存活
I got lucky.
卡西迪疯了
Cassidy's gone crazy.
他彻底失控了
He's gone insane.
他在南侧坡道
He's on the south ramp.
他去了那边
He went that way.
守着农
You stay with Nung.
闪开
Get out of the way!
别挡路
喂
Yes?
托尼 他在洋娃娃迪厅
Tony. He in Baby Doll now.
我们马上去
We'll be there.
好 快点 我等你
Okay, quick. I wait for you.
小心
Be careful.
波比
你是谁 怎么进来的
詹科在哪里
Where's Janko?
没有詹科 没有詹科
No Janko. No Janko.
没有詹科
No Janko.
不要说英语
No speak English.
他在哪里
Where is he?
他在仓库
He's at the warehouse.
靠河边的仓库
The warehouse, by the river.
他把货放在那里
Where he keeps his stock.
什么货
Stock?
年轻女孩
Young girls.
出去
Get out.
好了
Okay.
该死 我去你妈的
Fuck this, stupid motherfucker.
你要找的那个人 在詹科的办公室
The man you are looking for, he is in Janko's office.
但詹科不在
But Janko not here.
趴下
Get down!
把枪放下
Put your gun down!
你杀了农
You killed Nung!
我没杀那个警察
I didn't kill that cop.
我只想要维克多・德拉戈维奇和他儿子们的命
I just want Viktor Dragovic and his sons.
其余的我都不关心
After that I don't care.
那个警察是我朋友
That cop was my friend.
最后一次机会
Last chance.
回来
Get back!
托尼
Tony.
抓到他了吗
You get him?
你还好吗
You okay?
受伤了
You hit?
走吧
Come on.
一定会抓住他的
We're gonna get this guy.
去吧
Just go.
你留在这里
You stay here.
我去检查录像
I'll go check the tapes.
好的
Ok.
抓到你了
Gotcha.
你发现是谁泄露消息
Have you found out who's leaking the information
给警察了吗
to the police?
很好
Good.
我们会派人解决她的
We'll send someone for her now.
好的
Okay.
永远别小看变态
Never underestimate a pervert.
詹科在哪里
Where's Janko?
他在仓库
He's at the warehouse.
靠河边的
By the river.
他把货放在那里
Where he keeps his stock.
嘿
Hey.
我们走
Let's go.
要我吧 我年纪大 我妹妹太小
闭嘴 要我打断你的腿吗
想挨揍吗
闲的没事做吗
想要吗
去 去啊
Go, go, go!
别害怕 把枪给他
等等
Stay here.
詹科在哪里
Where's Janko?
你不是我弟弟
You're not my brother.
你是人尽可夫的婊子生的
You're the son of a whore who fucked everything up.
父亲不会这样的
Father would never!
父亲说晚安
Father says goodnight.
詹科 Victor在哪里
Janko! Where's Viktor?
嘿 詹科
Hey Janko!
停手吧
Get it over with.
你杀的那个人有妻子和小孩
The man you killed had a wife and kid!
另一个小孩下个月就要出生了
Another one coming in a month!
我说了我没有杀他
I told you I didn't kill him.
里德用他的枪杀了他
Reed shot him with his own weapon
然后给了我
and gave it to me.
趴下
Down!
告诉我你父亲去哪了
Tell me where your father's going!
詹科 听得见我说话吗
Janko! Can you hear me?
你父亲去哪了
Where's your father gone?
哪里
Where?
程... 程潮
Cheng... Cheng Chao.
程潮
Cheng Chao.
德拉戈维奇什么时候买通你的
When did Dragovic get you?
我猜我们都付出了代价 尼克
Guess we all have our price, Nick.
瞧瞧你的代价
Look at the price you paid.
你不该插手的
You should have got with the program.
就凭你俩就想阻止人皮交易
You think you two gonna stop the skin trade
就凭像童子军似的你们俩
just because you run around like fucking boy scouts?
你在乎那些姑娘吗
Fuck you care about these girls?
她们在哪里都生不如死
They'll just rot wherever they are anyway.
而你会在地狱里生不如死
And you will rot in hell.
他提到过一个机场
He mentioned an air strip.
程潮 你知道吗
Cheng Chao. You know it?
程潮
Cheng Chao.
在柬埔寨边境
The Cambodia border.
别乱动
Hold still.
为什么要这么做
Why are you doing this?
你受伤了
You're hurt.
不 我是说这个
No, this.
去边境线
Going to the border.
有可能我们两个都得死
Probably getting ourselves killed.
- 这是我的工作 - 狗屁
- It's my job. - Bullshit.
你面前的可是个警察
You're talking to a cop here.
有个叫敏的姑娘 我的线人
There's Min, my informant.
她是我女朋友
She's my girlfriend.
有些女孩并不是被绑架走的
You know, some of these girls are just not kidnapped.
而是被卖掉的
They are sold.
被谁卖掉的
Sold by who?
她们的父母
Their parents.
敏是被她母亲卖掉的
Min was sold by her mother.
现在她在他们手里 他们什么事都干得出来
Now I think they got her and they could do anything.
我喜欢有伤疤的人
I love people with scars.
我们是一样的 你和我
We are the same, you and I.
你心跳得很有力
You have a very strong heartbeat.
节奏中有种音乐感
There is a musicality to the rhythm.
咚咚 咚咚
Dum, dum. Dum, dum.
我们才不一样
We are not the same.
不吗
No?
但凡有心之人 不会做出你的行径
No one with a heart can do what you do.
沾血的钱仍然是钱
Blood money is still money.
但破烂货可没人要
But nobody wants damaged goods.
维克多
Viktor.
再会
Adieu.
托尼 有孩子
Tony! The kids!
好好听着
Listen, okay.
看见那些树了吗
You see those trees?
你们跑过去藏在后面
I want you to run and hide behind them.
记住回头看
I want you to look back.
记住这些人的脸
Remember the faces of these men.
如果我或者你父亲出了什么事
If something happens your father or me,
等你长大后 得为我们报仇
it is your duty to do something about it when you get older.
要牢牢记住 现在快跑
Remember. Now run!
老爸
Dad.
这里有一架直升机
It is a helicopter.
你可以看着我杀死她
You can watch me kill her.
- 快走 - 不 不
- Go. - No, no, no.
先生 还没加好油
Mister we aren't finished.
快走
Go!
真遗憾 你再也见不到你女儿了
Too bad you'll never see your daughter again.
她叫苏菲亚 对吗
Sofia, right?
她可是个极品货
She was a very fine piece of merchandise.
她在哪 她在哪
Where is she? Where is she?
她到底在哪
Where is she?!
四周后
所以她有可能还活着
So she could still be alive?
希望如此
I hope so.
我们要回去找到她
We'll be coming back to collect her.
永远别失去希望 尼克
Don't ever lose hope Nick.
我不知道她在哪
I don't know where she is.
但是我愿付出所有 追到天涯海角
But whatever it takes, wherever I have to go,
一定要把女儿找回来
I'm gonna find my daughter.
每年全世界人口贩卖涉及两千至三千万人
估计百分之九十八的色情贩卖受害者是妇女和儿童